{"test_questions": [[{"question": "A BI reporting system does not ________ .", "opta": "create meaningful information", "optb": "deliver information to users on a timely basis", "optc": "use statistical procedures to predict future events", "optd": "use disparate data sources", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following are not done by Business Intelligence (BI) systems?", "opta": "Analyze past and current activities only", "optb": "Process and record transactions only", "optc": "Both of the above are correct.", "optd": "Neither of the above is correct.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Business Intelligence (BI) systems do not obtain their data by which of the following means?", "opta": "Read and process data from an operational database", "optb": "Process transactions", "optc": "Process extracts from operational databases", "optd": "Process data purchased from data vendors", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The \"curse of dimensionality\" relates to which problem of using operational data for BI reporting?", "opta": "Dirty data", "optb": "Inconsistent data", "optc": "Too much data", "optd": "Non-integrated data", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A report generated by a reporting system is delivered to the appropriate users via a user-accessed Web site. This system uses which of the following report modes?", "opta": "Push", "optb": "Pull", "optc": "RFM", "optd": "OLAP", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "RFM analysis uses customers' purchasing patterns to ________ .", "opta": "record transactions", "optb": "analyze and rank customers", "optc": "predict future sales using regression techniques", "optd": "perform OLAP", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The \"F\" in RFM analysis stands for ________ .", "opta": "frequently", "optb": "freshness", "optc": "fast food", "optd": "fantasy", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "We have Market Basket data for 1,000 rental transactions at a Video Store. There are for videos for rent -- Video A, Video B, Video C and Video D. The probability that both Video C and Video D are rented at the same time is known as ________ .", "opta": "the basic probability", "optb": "support", "optc": "lift", "optd": "confidence", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Business Intelligence (BI) reporting systems cannot do which of the following operations?", "opta": "Filter data", "optb": "Group data", "optc": "Modify data", "optd": "Both filter and group data", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is not a component of a data warehouse?", "opta": "Data extraction/cleaning/preparation programs", "optb": "Data warehouse data", "optc": "Data metadata", "optd": "None of the above are data warehouse components.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Business Intelligence (BI) reporting analyses can be performed using ________ .", "opta": "standard SQL only", "optb": "extensions to SQL only", "optc": "OLAP only", "optd": "both standard SQL and extensions to SQL", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "We have been given access to the company's operational data, and have been asked to produce a report. We discover that some of the data we need are in an SQL server database while other needed data are in a separate Oracle database. This is an example of ________ .", "opta": "dirty data", "optb": "inconsistent data", "optc": "non-integrated data", "optd": "a \"wrong format\" problem", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The reports generated by a reporting system are usually not delivered in which of the following media?", "opta": "Web portal", "optb": "Commercial courier service", "optc": "Digital dashboard", "optd": "E-Mail", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Data mining applications are used accomplish which of the following tasks?", "opta": "Process transactions only", "optb": "Do RFM analysis only", "optc": "Do what-if analysis only", "optd": "Do both RFM and what-if analysis", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is an unsupervised data mining technique?", "opta": "Cluster analysis only", "optb": "Regression Analysis only", "optc": "RFM Analysis only", "optd": "Both Regression Analysis and RFM Analysis", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In OLAP, we are interested in ________ .", "opta": "levels only", "optb": "dimensions only", "optc": "measures only", "optd": "measures and dimensions", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is not a reason that operational data are difficult to read?", "opta": "Non-duplicated data", "optb": "Dirty data", "optc": "Missing values", "optd": "Non-integrated data", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "We have Market Basket data for 1,000 rental transactions at a Video Store. There are four videos for rent -- Video A, Video B, Video C and Video D. The probability that Video D will be rented given that Video C has been rented is known as ________ .", "opta": "the basic probability", "optb": "support", "optc": "lift", "optd": "confidence", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "One popular classification technique in Business Intelligence (BI) reporting is ________ .", "opta": "cluster analysis only", "optb": "regression analysis only", "optc": "RFM analysis only", "optd": "both cluster analysis and regression analysis", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "We have done an RFM analysis on our customer data. Mary Jones has a score of \"1 1 5\". This series means that Mary ________ .", "opta": "Has ordered recently, orders frequently, and places a large order when she orders.", "optb": "Hasn't ordered recently, orders infrequently, but places a large order when she orders.", "optc": "Has ordered recently, orders frequently, but doesn't place a large order when she orders", "optd": "Hasn't ordered recently, orders infrequently, and doesn't place a large order when she orders.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}